Now, there is another way of doing that.
Notice the layers in the back like I did it.
I like to do it like that.
It's a nice way of cutting this layered hair.
If you'd like, also, I have a process that you can do.
A layering that you can actually take the hair in an angle.
This is a, we're taught also when we cut hair.
We cut it like this.
Notice it's straight across.
This is a way of checking the way too if you want to see if it's even.
You can also cut the long layers like this and then go straight across and cut it.
Then we also continue to follow that guide and take the next piece over a little bit and into that way, and then see, but it's even.
That's another way of going ahead and cutting and knowing if you're even or not.
The way to check the hair.
After you cut it straight across, you go in another direction, and that's the way to check it actually.
You're going to go ahead and do the same thing here.
It will continue to be long.
See that?
I dropped that layer.
The layer will drop down and the length will still stay long and she will still have layered hair.